[music]
Welcome to this video. First of all,
what you have to do is type GSPL member login
in Google.
It is at the top. First of all, you will see a link,
that number is Login to Good Health.
You have to click on it. As soon as you click, the
Good Health website opens.
After the website opens, as soon as you scroll down the
page, you will see Login to Good Health.
There you will see Guddi and
Password. Right now, your password is
given in front of you. That is why it is given by saying '
ji'. What you have to do is
enter it here. For example,
I have added an associate here.
Right now, this is what you have done and the password which is your
default password for the first time is
1234. Those who have
logged in before and have changed their password will
log in with their password. Along with this, as soon as you
press the login button at the login place,
after pressing it, the page opens in such a way
that it is your home page. After the home page,
if you want to know your policy number, for that
you have to click on 'Cord Smile Policy'.
Yes, as soon as you click on the policy,
your page opens like this,
your policy information
is given, policy details and on this, the address,
corporate name, car, insurance
address, system details are given here,
you need two things, the
policy number, this is given by you,
when you want to make the claim not done, then at that time
you have to mention the policy number on your
form, on the claim form
and after this we go to flame, if
you have submitted any claim of anyone
and it is pending with GSPL, then to
know its status, you have to enter the details on flame,
click on flame and go to the
playlist, now if it is
given by any associate like you, then it is
given by two people, it is fine here, it
may be his own or of any of his family members,
what he has to do is
click on his pending claim on this file flame, I clicked it here,
after clicking, go to it, now
you can see that your
details are given here  Its claim IT is given,
claim type is given, claim status,
hospital name plate, mountains and distance, in this
also, when has the bill of patriots started, has the
bill been received, right now the
clean current status, that interface, if you make your
payment, which you will see in the previous one and if you
click on it, then your payment process will be
told, it can tell you the final stage,
so I am telling you how is yours,
now we have to go to them again,
click on it and you
will see the details here, now what will
you see here, at the time of incident, it is
your one and a half lakh rupees, okay, that
can be the change of company wife, which
client are you on, whatever client rise up
amount you have given, you will also see it here,
whatever it is, in this case the associate
amount is the first phase, right now your utilized
goods are also given, here it has been increased by 125
and the standing is FETU, that means the
action is in process, as if it will be settled,
it will be accounted for in the middle and certain
amount is 3000, okay and before this  Someday it will be
clear by combining all that your
remaining balance is 40, you have Vitamin
C and if we take into account the utilized amount in it then
your total balance comes
down here, in this way we
can see his prosperity,
how much respect is left and we will be
able to see the balance of mom, what
you have to do is simply if you want to download someone's
name
card, you have to download 18,
you will see these three buttons real dots,
you have to click on it and as
you click, you are cut off
on demand, as you click, in this way your
PDF file will open or
[music]
and you have to download it, as
you download, after downloading,
your agreement appears like this above and
you will see all these details here, now
you will be able to see on it, then all these details are
given, as it is named as set,
its example is Reddy, its
code number, since when is it boil and which company is it,
like the corporate name given in it is Team
Pure, okay,
then you will also get the details of its family member,
this is how it is,
you can download your ID card of whichever type you want here,
after downloading, we will go
back to the tab page and we have to click on home,
after clicking on home,
you will be given the mic profile here
and you can see the rest of the details here,
policy information download claim
form network6 shuttle search, network
search hospital, as we click here,
we can see which
hospitals are in the JSPL network, that is,
where this TPA
is available, from where we can do cashless treatment,
now we have to select some state,
what we have to do in the state, we have to
go to state
[music]
that Vyapam has taken it from Maharashtra, we have to
select any hospital in Maharashtra, so
if we want it in Pune, you will
click on Pune and from the hospitals of Pune,
all the hospitals which are eligible for JSPL will be
visible to you,
or there is a list of them, you have to straight line and
see the entire list, in this way you can see the hospitals
of Pune  You can search for the hospital after this,
you can search for any other hospital like
Solapur, Sindhudurg, Wardha, Yavatmal,
Nagpur, Parbhani, Pune, Mumbai, in this way you
can search for the details of any hospital here, city wise, right now
we can go to other states as well, in
this series we have selected
Uttar Pradesh, here we have to
select the name of the city, whatever it is,
Allahabad or Gonda, Jhansi, Kanpur, Lucknow, whatever it is,
we have searched in Lucknow, here the
names of the hospitals are sold in that way,
now here you have taken information about
which are your network hospitals of
GSPL where you
can avail the cashless facility, now we come back again
and you will see another one, policy information on home,
we have seen, you have to
check the details of the policy from here, after this you
download the claim, now as if you do any of the batsman, then
how will it be for reimbursement,
you get a form, you have to
fold the form, after clicking you have to
attach whatever document of the hospital you have.
ID proof has to be attached and it has to be
attached with the cancellation. If you are sending a claim of any of your
relatives like your wife or your children, then
what you have to do in it is that their ID proof has to be attached with it.
Now we will download the platform,
you will download it in it, the
platform opens,
now this is the claim form, now
you have to download this claim form and
what is the point of downloading, you have to click on details here,
like here you are
given the policy information first, you have to
enter the policy information, after this
your certificate number comes, this is
not required, there is no need in this, there is
no need to seal it, what you have to do is
then go to the seat, details of
families, and on the seat you can see
all the categories, now the company TID is given there, the
company clipBRD, now your
Health Good Help ID is given, on many the insurance
number is also written and then it can be written in the body, it can
also be the health card number,
so this is the same thing, this
device itself starts, you have to fill this
on your DP ID.  Name, your address,
city, your computer from mobile number and
email ID, this is required which
you have to submit at the time of insurance.
When you go to the insurance company, it asks for the status of insurance history. Here it is asked for current status.
It is a mediclaim hill pencil inside.
If you have any other mediclaim from
another company, you have to note it down like this.
You should not fill any details in it. Like if
you use it, then you will have to
see it and tell in which company he has a
health policy in another company in his mediclaim. You will have to
enter the voice number.
How much is the sum insured? Have you been hospitalized
in the last few years since the inception of the contract? How is it now? You have to give details in it, like in this film industry, you have to enter how are you in these four years, have
you taken any claim, have you been
hospitalized? You have to say yes
or no here and enter
whatever is there, its diagnosis, whatever will
not be your problem. This company has us
for whichever company you are, so if you
click on this above  If you do this then you have to enter the complete details
here, details
of introversion, hospitalized, how is it right now, as
whatever your question
is about family member cover, like you have been told
which of your family members are covered, then get
their answers prepared, if there is any
treatment claim, then in that case
you have to enter the details of their members,
details of three injured persons, now you have to
enter their name here, in this it can be
your wife, it
can be your children and whoever you want, it can be male
or female, you have to enter the date of birth,
date of birth has to be filled, after this the
relationship primary essence in your relation
means how is the primary member, that is, they
work in a company and it can be your wife, it can be of
whomever, this of
spouse is given, if there is a wife then you have to click on it,
you have to
select your children's and if your parents are covered
in that policy then you have to
select any of the father or mother whose
You are also planning this, you have to
put acid, after digital, details
of the position with his eyes from the hospital have to be
entered here,
like the name of the hospital where you
were admitted, after doing this, how is the room category for you, that
when you
take the complete hospital bill, it is
given in the bill that your essential was
single occupancy, turpentine setting, C
and more but there are general words like that, so there are
more than three-four, so I will definitely
tell you that it is of day care, whatever your
hospitalization is, now for what reason were
you admitted in this, due to injury, there was an
accident or injury, due to any disease,
glass terminated, means
how does this happen in a female, that when there is a delivery,
means what does it mean in this, when someone is
pregnant, she is someone's wife, then
in that case, there is a baby delivery, so what do
you have to do in that case, I have to
select the traffic jam, now the digital data
registration date of this is the first decade of
delivery  It is more like this
that you will be asked for an option that for what kind of
injury claim is it, is it a claim for this thing or is it a
claim for dirt, then you have to enter the
date of your first date, you have to
enter your illness or the day through which you had an
accident and on which day or
delete the data of the data delivery, you have to
enter the
retention date of admission, on the day
you admit the patient in the hospital, if he is a
living person or whatever, then you have to enter
his date of admission, you have to enter the time,
after this you have to enter the discharge data,
when was he discharged and the time
also have to be entered, ask the needle, type injury, give torch, if there is an injury, accident, then
what is the reason,
only incinerated, now how did it happen, is it
road providential or an
accidental case, if you were going on a bike and there was a
collision of the bike, then
you have to select it like this here, after this,
substance abuse, alcohol consumption,
whatever option you have, turn on the free channel
when alcohol is less in the population, then in that
Whatever it is, now this is a substance abuse case,
you have to select whatever is in number two,
after that medico
legal case, if a
file is required here, then you have to turn it on or off,
like in accidental cases, there is
damage here, for that
you need FD copy, now reported to
police and now your reported to police
option is given here, you have to click on
MLC Reports App and on it you have
clearly attached 28, you have to click on this, this
system of medicine, how is
your medication going on, whatever this retail shop,
ask the hospital, can you fill a
little clear claim, here you have to give
complete details, what
type of claim was it, what charges did you have to incur,
such preparations, how is
your policy, you will have to see what
type of expenses are covered, okay now it can be like
your free expenses,
except Monday, what are
your expenses that  They
go on during this war, whatever happens, you
leave the space between admission and discharge here,
how is it in other cases, it is possible that you have a
license letter from 30 days before admission,
like in cases where you have done your CT scan,
or whatever is the space of the mission, you
can send it by putting it in Play and it is
possible that after your consideration, you have
another cover of 7 days, then you can also put that together
but you will have to give the delivery information, in
what way, dear Brightness, famous,
if you have any, then you can put it, pass
license press, which was your admission,
how much space of Hussain you have to enter,
after this post Play Services, if
after hospitalization, with which pen
you have to enter the health checkup cost, if it is
in your health checkups, which recovery,
then you have to enter it here, ambulance
charges, if it is the ambulance which you
took with you to the hospital, if that ambulance is there,
whatever you can enter here, if
apart from this, you have to enter two from this tree
and also comment the total expense here,
now which clean documents have
you submitted, now which ones  You have submitted the document, first of all
you have to submit the copy of the elementary
mission to the PM Delhi side, if you have a copy of the Clementi mission, if you had
intimated someone in Nikle or if you have got a
copy of someone else, then what do you have to do,
like you submitted your film,
okay, then fill your online form,
what happens to this serial, you get it from that, if you
want, you can also attach a copy of that, that
you had intimated, okay,
today this is their intention with
you, what is it, it has been
registered with me, we are waiting for the
document, as it is,
process it here, okay, for the hospital also
you have to select, click here, what kind of
hospital backup bill, what kind of advisor, what was the
expenditure in your operation,
nursing charges, doctor, whatever it is, the
bill will be like that, hospital
breakup bill, okay, after your
hospital discharge, you also have to submit the
hospital bill payment receipt, the
bill you have made to the hospital, have you done it together,
one time or
part payment, whatever your bill
payment is, pharmacy bill,
operation theatre note will be applicable  If required, then
you have to submit the operation theatre notes as well as the
report of the same, if
yours is the same then you have to file a
doctor request for investigation, if
you have got any type of test done,
okay, if you have done a CBC test on your pathology WhatsApp, if
you have done a urine test, then you have to attach
its
investigation report and you have to
attach the bill
in the question reports,
this is our CT scan, if you have got anything done on that then
its bill and the report have to be attached along with it, you have to attach the
doctor's training
for the mission, others,
you can attach it from your other PAN, now here you have been given the
details of will receive inflows, now in this
you have to enter the bill number, first of all you have to enter the
issued by, the disposal of the
medicine you had purchased from the medical store,
so the name of the medical store is Nice Good
Bye and after this it is like this, yes suits,
now what kind of thing did you do,
put it there, it is visible everywhere in the first round, that
in the hospital, exactly
what kind of bill number you have to enter in the hospital  You have to
enter the name of the hospital issued by and for
what purpose they should get it in the hospital, just
enter that much, similarly
you have to enter all the things as
given here, omelette words, previous lives in
a specific course selection will pharmacy
beans, this side investigation report is
also like civil, you can enter it here,
this time
hospitals of premature bank account,
your Prasanna cover company has the main
person in which there is mediclaim in its name,
what you have to do is
enter your bank account details here and
before that you have to enter the PAN number, account number,
your bank account number, main
branch of the bank, cheque number, because if you have to pay
something at the time of cheque, without a cheque cancellation
cheque your claim does not get processed,
then you have to send the cheque number here, you have to
write in it the cheque which you are submitting,
after entering the IFSC code details,
you have to go to the necklace, there are
not many details in the next page, you have to
enter it here, whatever is your
location and here you have to leave the signature half an inch and do
not go like this, rest
you have to do it here  Guidelines have been given,
filing claim form part has been done on the guideline.